<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-19T02:45:43-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Al Pastor Tacos</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/al-pastor-tacos.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Al Pastor Tacos" /><published>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/al-pastor-tacos</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/al-pastor-tacos.html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to FoodBlog, fellow foodies! My name is Delores Samuels, and I’m excited to share with you one of my all-time favorite recipes: Al Pastor Tacos! If you’re looking for a delicious and easy-to-make meal that’s perfect for any occasion, then look no further. Al Pastor Tacos are a traditional Mexican dish that is packed with flavor and spice, and I’ve found the perfect recipe to recreate this authentic dish from Mexico City.</p>

<p>Al Pastor Tacos are a staple of Mexican street food, and they are incredibly popular throughout Mexico and beyond. The name “al pastor” literally means “shepherd style,” which refers to the way the meat is prepared. Traditionally, al pastor meat is cooked on a vertical spit, similar to the way shawarma or gyro meat is cooked, and then shaved off into thin slices. This style of cooking was brought to Mexico by Lebanese immigrants, and over time it has become an essential part of Mexican cuisine.</p>

<p>Now, let’s get started with this delicious and easy-to-make recipe for Al Pastor Tacos.</p>

<p>Ingredients:</p>

<p>1 pound pork shoulder, sliced thinly
1/2 cup pineapple juice
1/4 cup white vinegar
2 tbsp achiote paste
1 tbsp dried oregano
1 tbsp cumin
1 tbsp chili powder
4 cloves garlic, minced
1 onion, diced
Salt and pepper, to taste
Corn tortillas
Cilantro, chopped
Onion, diced
Lime wedges
Salsa of your choice
Instructions:</p>

<p>In a large bowl, combine the pineapple juice, white vinegar, achiote paste, oregano, cumin, chili powder, garlic, onion, salt, and pepper. Mix well.
Add the thinly sliced pork to the bowl and toss to coat the meat in the marinade. Cover the bowl with plastic wrap and refrigerate for at least 2 hours, but preferably overnight.
Preheat your grill to high heat. If you don’t have a grill, you can also cook the meat on a stovetop or in the oven.
Once the grill is hot, remove the pork from the marinade and discard any excess marinade. Thread the pork onto skewers and grill until cooked through, about 5 minutes per side. If you’re using a stovetop or oven, cook the pork in a skillet or baking dish until cooked through.
Remove the pork from the skewers and let it rest for a few minutes before slicing it thinly.
Warm up your tortillas on the grill, stovetop, or in the oven. Place a few slices of the al pastor meat onto each tortilla, and top with chopped cilantro and diced onion.
Serve your Al Pastor Tacos with lime wedges and your favorite salsa on the side.
Now, let me share some tips and tricks to make sure your Al Pastor Tacos come out perfectly.</p>

<p>Tip #1: Don’t skip the marinade</p>

<p>The marinade is what gives the pork its signature flavor and tenderness. Make sure you marinate the pork for at least 2 hours, but preferably overnight, to let the flavors fully develop.</p>

<p>Tip #2: Use achiote paste</p>

<p>Achiote paste is made from ground annatto seeds, which gives the pork its signature orange-red color. It’s an essential ingredient in this recipe, and you can find it at most Latin grocery stores or online.</p>

<p>Tip #3: Use a meat thermometer</p>

<p>When grilling or cooking the pork, use a meat thermometer to ensure it’s cooked to an internal temperature of 145°F.</p>]]></content><author><name>delores</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to FoodBlog, fellow foodies! My name is Delores Samuels, and I’m excited to share with you one of my all-time favorite recipes: Al Pastor Tacos! If you’re looking for a delicious and easy-to-make meal that’s perfect for any occasion, then look no further. Al Pastor Tacos are a traditional Mexican dish that is packed with flavor and spice, and I’ve found the perfect recipe to recreate this authentic dish from Mexico City.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Carne Asada Tacos</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/carne-asada-tacos.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Carne Asada Tacos" /><published>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/carne-asada-tacos</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/carne-asada-tacos.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hola amigos! It’s Delores Samuels back again on FoodBlog, and today I’m excited to share with you another one of my favorite taco recipes: Carne Asada Tacos! If you enjoyed my previous post on Al Pastor Tacos, then you’re going to love this one too.</p>

<p>Carne Asada is a classic Mexican dish that’s perfect for any occasion, whether it’s a casual weeknight dinner or a backyard barbecue. It’s made with grilled or seared flank steak that’s been marinated in a flavorful mixture of citrus, garlic, and spices.</p>

<p>Without further ado, let’s dive into the recipe!</p>

<p>Ingredients:</p>

<p>1 lb flank steak
1/4 cup lime juice
1/4 cup orange juice
2 tbsp soy sauce
2 cloves garlic, minced
1 tbsp cumin
1 tbsp chili powder
1/2 tsp paprika
Salt and pepper, to taste
Corn tortillas
Cilantro, chopped
Onion, diced
Lime wedges
Salsa of your choice
Instructions:</p>

<p>In a large bowl, whisk together the lime juice, orange juice, soy sauce, garlic, cumin, chili powder, paprika, salt, and pepper.
Add the flank steak to the bowl and toss to coat the meat in the marinade. Cover the bowl with plastic wrap and refrigerate for at least 2 hours, but preferably overnight.
–Just like in my previous post, the marinade is crucial for this recipe. It’s what gives the meat its delicious flavor and tenderness.–</p>

<p>Preheat your grill to high heat. If you don’t have a grill, you can also cook the meat on a stovetop or in the oven.
Once the grill is hot, remove the steak from the marinade and discard any excess marinade. Grill the steak for about 4-6 minutes per side, or until it reaches your desired level of doneness.
Remove the steak from the grill and let it rest for a few minutes before slicing it thinly against the grain.
Warm up your tortillas on the grill, stovetop, or in the oven. Place a few slices of the carne asada onto each tortilla, and top with chopped cilantro and diced onion.
Serve your Carne Asada Tacos with lime wedges and your favorite salsa on the side.
Now, let me share some tips and tricks to make sure your Carne Asada Tacos come out perfectly.</p>

<p>Tip #1: Don’t overcook the meat</p>

<p>Flank steak is a lean cut of meat, so it can easily become tough and chewy if overcooked. Keep an eye on the steak while grilling it, and remove it from the grill once it reaches your desired level of doneness.</p>

<p>Tip #2: Slice against the grain</p>

<p>When slicing the steak, be sure to slice against the grain to ensure the meat stays tender and easy to chew.</p>

<p>Tip #3: Customize your toppings</p>

<p>Feel free to get creative with your toppings! You can add sliced avocado, crumbled queso fresco, or even a dollop of sour cream to your tacos for extra flavor and creaminess.</p>

<p>I hope you enjoy this recipe for Carne Asada Tacos! It’s a classic Mexican dish that’s perfect for any occasion, and I’m sure it will become a favorite in your household. Hasta luego!</p>]]></content><author><name>delores</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hola amigos! It’s Delores Samuels back again on FoodBlog, and today I’m excited to share with you another one of my favorite taco recipes: Carne Asada Tacos! If you enjoyed my previous post on Al Pastor Tacos, then you’re going to love this one too.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How To Make Authentic New York Style Bagels</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/how-to-make-authentic-new-york-style-bagels.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Make Authentic New York Style Bagels" /><published>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/how-to-make-authentic-new-york-style-bagels</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/how-to-make-authentic-new-york-style-bagels.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="how-to-make-authentic-new-york-style-bagels">How to Make Authentic New York-Style Bagels</h1>

<p>If there’s one thing that New York City is famous for, it’s bagels. These chewy, dense, and delicious breads are a staple of the city’s cuisine and are beloved by locals and tourists alike. But despite their popularity, many people outside of New York have never tasted a real New York-style bagel. If you’re one of those people, fear not – with this recipe, you can make authentic New York-style bagels right in your own kitchen.</p>

<p>##Ingredients</p>

<p>To make a batch of 12 bagels, you’ll need:</p>

<ul>
  <li>4 cups bread flour</li>
  <li>1 tablespoon sugar</li>
  <li>1 1/2 teaspoons salt</li>
  <li>2 teaspoons instant yeast</li>
  <li>1 1/4 cups water</li>
  <li>1 egg white</li>
  <li>Poppy seeds, sesame seeds, or other toppings (optional)</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="instructions">Instructions</h2>

<h3 id="step-1-mix-the-dough">Step 1: Mix the Dough</h3>
<p>In a large mixing bowl, combine the bread flour, sugar, salt, and instant yeast. Mix the dry ingredients together thoroughly. Then, slowly add in the water, stirring the mixture constantly until it forms a shaggy dough. Turn the dough out onto a floured surface and knead it for about 10 minutes, or until it becomes smooth and elastic.</p>

<h3 id="step-2-let-the-dough-rise">Step 2: Let the Dough Rise</h3>
<p>Place the dough in a lightly oiled bowl and cover it with a damp cloth or plastic wrap. Let the dough rise in a warm place for about an hour, or until it has doubled in size.</p>

<h3 id="step-3-shape-the-bagels">Step 3: Shape the Bagels</h3>
<p>Once the dough has risen, turn it out onto a floured surface and divide it into 12 equal pieces. Roll each piece into a ball, then use your fingers to poke a hole through the center of each ball. Gently stretch the hole until it is about 2 inches in diameter. Place the bagels on a floured baking sheet and cover them with a damp cloth. Let them rest for about 10 minutes.</p>

<h3 id="step-4-boil-the-bagels">Step 4: Boil the Bagels</h3>
<p>While the bagels are resting, bring a large pot of water to a boil. Preheat your oven to 425°F. Once the water is boiling, use a slotted spoon to lower the bagels into the pot, a few at a time. Boil the bagels for 1-2 minutes on each side, or until they have puffed up slightly and the dough is set. Use the slotted spoon to remove the bagels from the water and place them back on the baking sheet.</p>

<h3 id="step-5-add-toppings">Step 5: Add Toppings</h3>
<p>If you want to add toppings to your bagels, now is the time to do it. Brush each bagel with egg white and sprinkle with poppy seeds, sesame seeds, or any other topping of your choice.</p>

<h3 id="step-6-bake-the-bagels">Step 6: Bake the Bagels</h3>
<p>Bake the bagels in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes, or until they are golden brown and crispy on the outside. Remove the bagels from the oven and let them cool on a wire rack for a few minutes before serving.</p>

<h2 id="tips-for-success">Tips for Success</h2>

<p>Use bread flour instead of all-purpose flour. This will give your bagels a chewy texture.
Let the dough rise in a warm place. If your kitchen is too cold, your dough won’t rise properly.
Don’t over-boil the bagels. They should only be in the boiling water for 1-2 minutes on each side. Any longer and they may become too dense.
Be creative with your toppings! In addition to poppy seeds and sesame seeds, you can also use salt, garlic, onion, or even chocolate</p>]]></content><author><name>ted</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Authentic New York-Style Bagels]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Make Shrimp Tacos</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/shrimp-tacos.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Make Shrimp Tacos" /><published>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2023-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/shrimp-tacos</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/19/shrimp-tacos.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello foodies! It’s Delores Samuels again on FoodBlog, and today I’m excited to share with you a mouth-watering recipe for Shrimp Tacos. After sharing my favorite Al Pastor and Carne Asada taco recipes, I wanted to mix it up with some seafood. This recipe is simple, quick, and oh-so-delicious!</p>

<p>Ingredients:</p>

<ul>
  <li>1 lb large shrimp, peeled and deveined</li>
  <li>1 tbsp olive oil</li>
  <li>1 tbsp chili powder</li>
  <li>1 tsp cumin</li>
  <li>1/2 tsp garlic powder</li>
  <li>Salt and pepper, to taste</li>
  <li>Corn tortillas</li>
  <li>Cabbage, thinly sliced</li>
  <li>Avocado, sliced</li>
  <li>Red onion, thinly sliced</li>
  <li>Cilantro, chopped</li>
  <li>Lime wedges</li>
  <li>Chipotle crema (see recipe below)</li>
</ul>

<p>Chipotle Crema Ingredients:</p>

<ul>
  <li>1/2 cup sour cream</li>
  <li>2 tbsp adobo sauce (from canned chipotle peppers)</li>
  <li>1 tbsp lime juice</li>
  <li>Salt, to taste</li>
  <li>Instructions:</li>
</ul>

<p>In a small bowl, whisk together the olive oil, chili powder, cumin, garlic powder, salt, and pepper. Add the shrimp to the bowl and toss to coat.
Heat a large skillet over medium-high heat. Once the skillet is hot, add the shrimp and cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until the shrimp are pink and cooked through.
–Just like in my previous taco recipes, it’s important not to overcook the shrimp. Overcooked shrimp can become tough and rubbery.–</p>

<p>Warm up your tortillas on the skillet or in the oven. Once the tortillas are warm, place a few shrimp onto each tortilla.
Top the shrimp with thinly sliced cabbage, sliced avocado, red onion, and chopped cilantro.
Serve your Shrimp Tacos with a squeeze of lime juice and a dollop of chipotle crema.
To make the chipotle crema, simply whisk together the sour cream, adobo sauce, lime juice, and salt in a small bowl. Adjust the seasoning to taste.</p>

<p>And there you have it, a quick and delicious recipe for Shrimp Tacos. This recipe is perfect for a quick weeknight meal or for entertaining guests. So give it a try and let me know what you think!</p>]]></content><author><name>delores</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello foodies! It’s Delores Samuels again on FoodBlog, and today I’m excited to share with you a mouth-watering recipe for Shrimp Tacos. After sharing my favorite Al Pastor and Carne Asada taco recipes, I wanted to mix it up with some seafood. This recipe is simple, quick, and oh-so-delicious!]]></summary></entry></feed>